{
    "subject": "resource/Alexander_Cambridge,_1st_Earl_of_Athlone",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/London",
    "human_readable": "Alexander Cambridge, 1st Earl of Athlone was born in London.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7642754912376404,
            "question": "Where was Alexander Cambridge born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6761492490768433,
            "question": "In what century was Alexander Cambridge born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5551623702049255,
            "question": "Was Alexander Cambridge a descendant of royalty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44402652978897095,
            "question": "What other notable individuals were related to Alexander Cambridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4054717421531677,
            "question": "What was the name of Alexander Cambridge's ancestral home?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37745824456214905,
            "question": "What title did Alexander Cambridge hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.266560822725296,
            "question": "What role did Alexander Cambridge play in British society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2643786072731018,
            "question": "What were some of the major events that occurred during Alexander Cambridge's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2580258250236511,
            "question": "What is known about Alexander Cambridge's personal life and interests?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15730923414230347,
            "question": "Did Alexander Cambridge hold any military positions?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alexander Cambridge, 1st Earl of Athlone was born in London.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6661_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Alexander Cambridge's personal life and interests?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6661_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the major events that occurred during Alexander Cambridge's lifetime?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6661_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role did Alexander Cambridge play in British society?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6661_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6661_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6661_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6661_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6661_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6661_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6661_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6661_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6661_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6661_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6661_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide information about Alexander Cambridge, 1st Earl of Athlone's birth, stating that he was born on 14 April 1874 in London. Therefore, the triple \"Alexander Cambridge, 1st Earl of Athlone was born in London\" is supported by the context information and can be considered correct according to the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Alexander Cambridge, 1st Earl of Athlone, was born in London. For example, one document states, \"Prince Alexander was born to the Duke and Duchess of Teck and was educated at Eton College and the Royal Military College, Sandhurst.\" Another confirms this by saying, \"He was a British Army commander, who served as Governor-General of the Union of South Africa and Governor General of Canada. Prince Alexander was born in London to Francis, Duke of Teck and Princess Mary Adelaide of Cambridge and was educated at Eton College and the Royal Military College, Sandhurst.\" Therefore, the information supports the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}